## Sella Rafaeli, CV: Web Developer / CTO / Consultant

sella.rafaeli@gmail.com, https://sellarafaeli.com

### Skills

I have +15 years of experience of full-stack web development and management; backend, frontend, product. Ex-8200, HUJI, Fiverr.

I am an expert in Ruby (Rails, Sinatra), Python (Flask, Django), JavaScript (Vanilla, Vue, React, Anguları, Anguları, Node), AWS/Heroku, and full-stack web development in general.

### Education

OCT 2009 - JUL 2012

**Hebrew University, Jerusalem - BSc Computer Science**, graduated Magna Cum Laude

JUL 2008

786 / 800 on Israeli's SAT (National Psychometric Exam), top 0.01%.

# **Experience**

APRIL 2016 - PRESENT

#### **Consultant, Team8**

- Working with multiple clients, providing consulting or development.
- Clients include Israeli cyber-security firms (including Hysolate, Cymmetria, RealFace [now Apple]), private e-commerce marketplaces, and B<sub>2</sub>C apps.

MARCH 2015 - APRIL 2016

#### Founder & CTO, yes.no

- Founder, CTO, recruited and managed R&D team of 6.
- Crowd-Interviewing Platform
- Raised 1M\$. Sold, private.

2012 - MARCH 2015

#### Senior Full-Stack Web Developer, Fiverr

- Led development on banking, payment and order flows
- Led development on Innovation Team

2009 - 2012

### Hebrew University, BSc Computer Science

- Graduated Magna Cum Laude
- Minor in Psychology

2003 - 2008

#### **IDF, 8200**

- Intelligence Officer; please ask for references.
- Receiver of multiple IDF awards.

# **Published Works**

- My published articles: <a href="https://sellarafaeli.com/blog/">https://sellarafaeli.com/blog/</a>
- My e-book on Linear Algebra: <a href="https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/">https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/</a>
- My e-book on Algorithms: <a href="https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/see-also">https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/see-also</a>
- My e-book on Git: <a href="https://sellarafaeli.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/git-sandbox-book/">https://sellarafaeli.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/git-sandbox-book/</a>